Contact

3618460120 (Home) krisrn4@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kristin-gibson-b89354100 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care

ICU

ACLS

Languages

Spanish

English

Certifications

NIH Stroke Certification
Basic EKG Certification

Kristin Gibson

ICU Registered Nurse

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced ICU Registered Nurse with 10 years of demonstrated history of working in Acute care facilities, specializing in critical care and critical care float Pool. Skilled in Ventilator management, Level 1 facility ICU, Patient Advocacy, Medication Administration, Pediatrics, Patient Education, and Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS). ACLS Certified currently and TNCC Certification complete Spring 2019.

Experience

Parallon Workforce Solutions Registered Nurse 2015 - Present (5 years) Houston, Texas Area

Local per diem

Bayshore Medical Group ICU Registered Nurse November 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months) Pasadena. TX

Full Time

The University of Texas Medical Branch Critical care float pool RN March 2017 - June 2019 (2 years 4 months) Galveston, Texas

Float to all critical care units. MICU, SICU, Neuro ICU, and Burns ICU. Also floated to all acute care nursing units.

Driscoll Children's Hospital
PICU Registered Nurse
March 2014 - August 2014 (6 months)
Corpus Christi, Texas Area

UnityPoint Health Registered Nurse February 2007 - October 2013 (6 years 9 months) West Des Moines, Iowa

Charge Nurse/Acute Care RN. MedSurg/Tele RN. Floated to inpatient acute care units. Neuro/surgical/trauma/ortho, pulmonary care, oncology, postpartum, telemetry.

Education

Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2019 - 2020)

Mercy College of Health Sciences
Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2008 - 2010)